I'll show you the easiest way for you to make the sale
come with me bro
is always a great choice
there are always people there
arrive agorinha
here in the optics
that I cleaned the window
the guy was good people
and now I will show my product
and then my good
how are you
authorized seller
Cocoa Show Guy
and then I wanted to show you some troupes
I scratched here
thanks there
success
tamo together
twenty-five
twenty-nine hand
I learned a lot mano
it's all about strategy
you don't even have to be that creative
knows how you relate to people
all this to sell truffle
clear hand
a doctor studied
six years to be able to have his first surgery
do you think you'll only get a truffle
and sell out on the street
and will have resulted brother
you need to have strategy bro
my bet goes here
where I'm relating
there's a barber shop down here and I'm going there
agorinha
and that's it bro
it's giving good doidão
and there's bonzão there
wants
do in pix
sorry
but i'll get a little card machine
the bag here is light bro
real food
car stopped
I will make a return here
and then something we combine within a day
there it's good
for me
no face
you can't catch this car flashing here